WOMAN 1: A young American
on an evangelical mission,
his adventures taking
a harrowing turn.
WOMAN 2:
...who loved the outdoors.
MAN 1:
John Chau traveled the world.
It's a journey
that ended in tragedy.
WOMAN 1: American
John Allen Chau was killed--
MAN 2: ...killed after traveling
to an off-limits remote tribe
in the Bay of Bengal.
WOMAN 3:
It was incredibly dangerous.
WOMAN 4:
It's illegal, for good reason.
WOMAN 5: He wanted
to share the love of God...
MAN 3: No one asked this kid
to go North Sentinel Island...
MAN 4: ...Chau never should've
ventured out to the island.
MAN 5:
Just trying to spread his faith.
WOMAN 6:
Incredibly misguided attempt.
MAN 4: Called him a martyr
tonight, the founder saying...
WOMAN 6: He wasn't a martyr,
he was an idiot.
WOMAN 5: This is what God
had called him to do.
WOMAN 7: John Chau is yet
another example of the evil
influence of neocolonialism.
MAN 5: He's... He's a hero.
WOMAN 8:
Put his money where his mouth...
MAN 6:
What did you expect to happen?
MAN 7: He's a nutjob!
MAN 8: He was an inspiration.
WOMAN 1:
But the question now is...
Who was John Chau?
(WATER LAPPING)
(MAN EXHALES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BIRD TWEETS)
(EXHALES)
(BIRDS TWEETING)
Hello!
Anybody home?
(HUMMING HYMN)
(CONTINUES HUMMING)
(CONTINUES HUMMING, SIGHS)
Good morning!
(PANTING)
I'm John!
I love you!
Jesus sent me to you! (CHUCKLES)
Here I am.
Uh, I have gifts.
-(SPEAKS NATIVE LANGUAGE)
-(TRIBESPEOPLE LAUGH)
-(REPEATS WORD)
-(TRIBESPEOPLE SHOUT)
Yeah?
(REPEATS WORD)
Here.
Fish.
It's okay.
It's for you.
It's all for you.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, my gosh.
"For God so loved the world,
he gave his one and only son,
that whoever believes in him
shall not perish
but shall have ever--"
-(TRIBESPEOPLE GRUNTING)
-No? No.
No! No!
-(ARROW WHIRS)
-(BLOW LANDS)
-(ARROWS WHIR)
-(JOHN GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS, SHOUTS)
(INHALES)
(CLANKS)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
-(HORNS HONKING)
-(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
-(MOTORCYCLE WHIRS)
(WOMEN CHUCKLING,
CHATTER IN HINDI)
New Delhi wants us
to test backup power.
Relax! Don't worry.
Just a small test.
Don't worry.
Ready?
Get back to work.
What is wrong with this?
Just a spark, not fire.
Take it back.
(MOUSE CLICKING)
-Okay.
-(DIALING NUMBER)
(LINE RINGS)
-MAN: Steve Simon.
-US Consulate?
Yeah, Steve Simon.
This is Inspector Ganali,
Port Blair police,
Andaman Islands.
You have an alert
on a missing citizen.
MAN: Correct.
Has anyone else
contacted you yet?
-Get back to work.
-MAN: No, you'd be the first.
Kid's a missionary.
We got a tip he might be headed
to North Sentinel Island.
(HORNS HONKING)
No. We have no John Chau
staying here.
Perhaps he's using another name.
Perhaps he's staying
at another hotel.
This man does not
want attention.
Other hotels require
credit cards
and passports, not yours.
This is how he looks like.
Ma'am, as you can see,
there are so many people
pass through here
on a daily basis.
So, maybe. I don't know.
Okay. Fine.
Then we'll go room by room
until we find him.
-HOTEL CLERK: Look, madam...
-Excuse me, ma'am.
I think I recognize him.
-Him?
-Yes, ma'am. This guy.
He had me call a taxi for him.
-Did he say where he was going?
-(CLERK SCOFFS)
Unlikely.
YOUNG MAN:
To the airport, ma'am.
He should be in charge. Not you.
Thank you.
Are you done, sir?
-(HORNS HONKING)
-(ANNOUNCER SPEAKS, INDISTINCT)
I'm looking for
an American male.
Last name is "Chau". C-H-A-U.
First name is John or Jonathan.
John Chau. C-H-A-U.
Nothing here.
Not booked on
anything going out today.
Just show me all the Americans
traveling today.
(BEEPING)
Sir, passport, please?
Yeah, sure.
Sir, come with me, please.
Is there a problem?
Take your bag
and come with me, please.
(AMERICAN EXHALES)
Chandler Synnes...
Synnestvedt.
And your reason for coming here?
Just stopping off for a few days
before heading to Thailand.
You only arrived this morning.
You're flying out again?
Yeah,
it's just a change of plans.
I had to get to Thailand
sooner than I thought.
Your trip originated
in Tanzania?
Mm-hmm.
I'm currently based there, yeah.
And what's your profession?
I'm a missionary.
Is that a crime?
Going to North Sentinel Island
is a crime.
Helping someone get there
is also a crime.
What's that got to do with me?
-Chandler?
-Yeah?
Where is John Chau?
Who?
MAN: ♪ Praise God,
for all blessings flow ♪
ALL: ♪ Praise Him,
all creatures here below ♪
♪ Praise Him, above,
ye heavenly hosts ♪
♪ Praise Father,
Son and Holy Ghost ♪
(CHEERING)
Yeah!
(APPLAUSE FADES)
Soli Deo Gloria.
"Glory to God alone."
On the eve of our graduation,
as we prepare to go out
and make our mark in the world,
we remember
what Jesus himself said,
in sending his own disciples
out into the world,
"Go where my light is dim,
and my voice is small."
-(LIGHT SWITCHES CLICK)
-MAN: Whoa.
Would all of you
reach down underneath your seats
and take out
what you find there.
This next part
is entirely optional.
If this isn't for you,
be honest, don't participate.
If you're ready to say yes,
to commit to illuminating
the darkest corners
of a broken, hurting world...
...light your candle.
If you pledge with me
to hear the cries of the damned
as they hurtle headlong
into the Christless night...
...light your candle.
(TRUCK HORN BLOWS)
(BRAKE SQUEALS)
Why didn't you
just light the candle?
(SIGHS)
What are you trying to prove?
(INHALES, EXHALES)
-No!
-(GROUP CHUCKLES)
-Are you serious?
-FRIEND: Hello, man.
-JOHN: (LAUGHS)
-FRIEND: Good to see you, buddy.
(GROUP CHUCKLES)
WOMAN: There he is. Come here.
Hi, sweetheart. Hi.
Oh, so great to see you.
-You okay?
-Yeah, I'm good.
Guys, thank you so much
for coming all the way out here.
Hey, Dad.
Thank you for joining us.
Sorry.
DAD: Heavenly Father,
thank you for this meal.
For the family gathered here
on John's graduation.
May you continue
guiding him on his journey.
-Amen.
Amen.
(PERSON LAUGHS)
(MOANS) REI?
Thank you, Brian and Marilyn!
Well, what time is it?
Are they still open?
Can we make it there?
-This one's from me.
-Mom.
(MOM CHUCKLES)
-You like it?
-Oh... my... gosh.
To write your own
adventure novel with.
It's gonna need some more pages.
(GROUP CHUCKLES)
JOHN: Thank you, Mom.
This one... is from your father.
It's what I've always wanted.
I never had one that nice.
(GROUP CHUCKLES)
-JOHN: ...so much.
-FRIEND: Love you, man.
Still cannot believe
you flew out.
(FRIEND CHUCKLES)
-See you soon.
-We'll see you soon.
-Bye.
-See you later. Bye.
Mom, I wanna let you know,
I'm not coming back.
To the hotel?
I'm not coming back home
after school ends.
Where are you going?
Kurdistan.
There's a missionary program
that helps organize support
for refugee kids.
You mean, for the summer?
I'm not going to medical school.
-John.
-You have to break it to Dad.
Sweetheart,
you've already been admitted.
I don't want to be a doctor.
I'm not like Brian or Marilyn,
okay?
I'm not perfect like them.
John.
When I'm out there
in the wilderness,
that's when
I feel closest to God.
That's where I belong.
We've talked about this.
-You can't go.
-I'm telling you.
This is not-- It's--
DAD: Lynda!
-LYNDA: Okay. Okay.
-Let's go.
(MOUTHING)
-LYNDA: Okay.
-JOHN: Okay. Okay, yeah.
-We'll talk.
-Okay.
(SIGHS)
I'm not going.
Welcome all of you
to your first day
of medical school.
This is the beginning
of a very long,
but ultimately,
very rewarding career
as a doctor,
one of the most vital
and important roles in society.
(CUTLERY CLINKING)
Have you studied
cadaver work yet?
Just wait.
It takes a bit,
but after your residency,
you'll see.
Being a doctor will open up
the world for you.
I'm sure the Lord
will reveal John's path
when the time is right.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Who could that be?
I will see.
John.
Your father just wants
the best for you.
I'll be back.
Where're you going?
-Patrick?
-PATRICK: It's fine.
Uh... Just a misunderstanding.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
John?
They're saying he illegally
prescribed painkillers
to undercover agents.
I think they
might file criminal charges.
Where do we keep those
little things of toothpaste?
LYNDA: What?
What's going on?
John?
He never paints anymore.
LYNDA: What? What do you mean?
John.
John!
-John, where are you going?
-(BAG THUDS)
I never should've have
doubted Him, Mom.
God's always there.
-(DOOR SHUTS)
-(ENGINE STARTS)
(RADIO CHATTER)
-(BANGS TABLE)
-(CHANDLER GROANS)
Is this the two of you together?
-All right, yeah, I know him.
-Mmm.
I came out here to stop him.
From going to North Sentinel?
Well, he hid it from everybody.
As soon as I realized
what he was doing,
I rushed out here.
Why would you stop him?
That's exactly
what you people do,
push your beliefs on others.
No, I did not want John
to get hurt.
Oh, so you talked him out of it?
I couldn't find him.
I went to his hotel--
I went to his hotel.
He's not there.
He's not answering his phone!
I didn't know what else to do,
so I came back to the airport.
(SIGHS)
Now I've missed my flight.
This is John's backpack.
(GROANS)
Believe me,
I can do much worse than that.
Now, come with me.
Okay, look,
let's just calm down.
Will you just sit back down--
Up!
(SIGHS, CLEARS THROAT)
(JOHN, CHILDREN SHOUTING)
Come on, come on.
It's yours! Take it, take it.
Abdul! Abdul! Yeah!
(CHILDREN SHOUTING)
WOMAN: Almost done, Kayla.
(MAN SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
-(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
-JOHN: Let's go. Let's go.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING IN DISTANCE)
Reading anything good?
Isaiah?
Chapter?
Sixty-five.
"I revealed myself to those
who did not ask for me.
I was found by those
who did not seek me.
To a nation
that did not call my name,
I said, 'Here am I, here am I.'"
-I'm John.
-I know.
Wanna go for a ride?
(ENGINE SPUTTERS, STARTS)
Hop on.
Hold on tight to me, okay?
Hope you don't mind.
This is a bit of
an off-books operation.
If you ask me, what's the point
of saving somebody's body
but not their soul?
(JOHN CHUCKLES)
Is this legal?
Sometimes
you gotta just jump in,
ready or not.
North Sentinel Island.
No one's ever got that before.
(CHUCKLES) Come on. That's--
The ultimate mission.
(RUMBLING ECHOES)
What's that noise?
CHANDLER: NATO jets.
F-22s.
-(EXPLOSIONS ECHO)
-Bombing ISIS in Mosul.
Mosul's 150 miles from here.
Imagine
what it sounds like there.
John, this is Chandler.
(EXPLOSIONS CONTINUE)
You want to take a ride?
-In this?
-Uh-huh.
Put this on.
It's in case we crash,
they can find your body.
(SEATBELT UNBUCKLES)
We're currently flying
over ancient Mesopotamia,
headwaters of the Tigris
and Euphrates river.
You know what Genesis 2:14
calls that place?
Eden.
We've got
the God's-eye view of it.
Hey, you wanna fly her a bit?
What?
You wanna fly her a bit?
(SCOFFS, CHUCKLES)
Are you crazy?
Sure.
Grab the yoke.
There you go. Keep her steady.
Okay. Good.
Okay.
I'm letting go. All right?
Yeah, I got it.
I got it.
CHANDLER:
All right. There you go.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You're flying the plane now.
Should be right over
the drop zone.
Drop zone? Cha--
Good job.
Cha-- Chandler!
There's two kinds
of missionaries
in this world, John.
One's all those NGO bureaucrats
on the ground down there,
sealed off in their compounds,
handing out...
water bottles and soccer balls.
What's the other kind?
Well, God doesn't make
many of them, that's for sure.
(PLANE ENGINE HUMMING)
(ENGINE RATTLING)
This other type of missionary.
What do they do?
Should I not be asking?
CHANDLER:
Here we are in Kurdistan...
-Right?
-JOHN: Mm-hmm.
CHANDLER:
Show me where else you've been.
Nice. Hawaii.
Mexico.
Dominican Republic. Corsica.
Okay, anywhere else?
No, that's it.
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
-North Korea?
-CHANDLER: Uh-huh.
Papua New Guinea.
Brazil.
Brazilian Amazon.
Tribe called the Pirahã.
You've been to all these places?
No, of course not.
Christian missionaries
aren't allowed
to go to those areas.
Not gonna find those stamps
in our passports.
Let me ask you something.
This day and age,
what makes someone a saint?
You know, what kind of risks
are you willing to take?
How far behind enemy lines
are you willing to go?
(HORNS HONKING IN DISTANCE)
-What the hell is this thing?
-(DOG PANTING)
He's immensely strong.
The real deal. Just look at him.
This is a crowd-control dog.
I asked for a drug-sniffing dog.
Can he not do both?
It's a she. It's a female.
What shall we name it, sir?
It's not getting a name.
It's going back
to where it came from.
-Okay.
-(DOG BARKING EXCITEDLY)
Look at that.
He doesn't like her.
-About the American, sir.
-(SIGHS)
(RADIO CHATTER, INDISTINCT)
John Chau.
Doesn't look very American.
I spoke to the US Consulate,
sir. And I--
Tell me, sub-inspector,
how many islands
have we jurisdiction over?
836, sir.
And this John Chau of yours,
he could have gone
to any one of them.
GANALI: But he didn't.
Of the top ten
uncontacted tribes
targeted by the missionaries
for conversion to Christianity,
one is right here
on North Sentinel.
I can't believe
we made the top ten list.
Ishaan, Farid,
go to the North Sentinelese
and tell them
of their good fortune.
Sir, he may still be here
in Port Blair. He may be waiting
to leave at night.
And when he does,
he'll be intercepted
by the coast guard,
which has a very tight blockade
around North Sentinel.
But it's much more likely
he's just another tourist,
here to drink, cavort,
and lie on the beach.
May I at least alert
the navy and coast guard
to be on the lookout for someone
attempting to reach the island?
If we issued an alert every time
some American brat
forgets to call home,
we'd never rest.
Farid!
For the love of God,
remove this canine
from my office.
This fellow, as you call him,
has been casing the wharf
for a boat crew
to take him to North Sentinel.
(EXHALES)
And how do you know that?
(MAN SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(BOTH SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(MEN SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(MEN CONTINUE SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
GANALI (ON RADIO):
Sir? Sir, come in, sir.
Yes, sub-inspector?
GANALI: Sir, we found the crew.
Main pier on the east side.
Main pier
on the east side, sir.
(STATIC HISSES)
What is this?
What are you hiding?
-Don't lie to me.
-These poor guys?
Harbor surveillance cameras
show this boat
departing Friday at midnight,
running lights off,
and returning at sunrise.
So they confessed to taking
John Chau to North Sentinel?
Oh, they will. Once they've seen
the inside of a jail cell.
Give me that thing.
"Running lights"?
The lights barely work
on this rust bucket.
After four months, you still
don't know where you are,
sub-inspector.
This is Port Blair.
This is the edge of the world.
Policing is not about technology
or interrogation tactics.
It's about people.
Can you even speak
their language?
No.
(SPEAKS FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
They indeed took John Chau
out on their boat.
See? What did I tell you?
And then they brought him
back to Port Blair.
Brought him back?
He has returned to Port Blair
having most likely
learned his lesson.
I think we're finished here.
How do you know
they brought him back?
They could be lying
to avoid getting in trouble.
They are already
in trouble, miss.
Then where is he?
He came back here,
got off the boat. Then what?
Like I said, sub-inspector,
check the bars,
check the beaches,
check the souvenir shops.
It's there you'll find
your missing John Chau.
(SIGHS) Sir... he'll try again.
I doubt it.
GANALI: Read his journal.
He believes God sent him here
to save the souls
of the Sentinelese.
Young people believe
all kinds of things.
Then they wise up.
This other one, Chandler.
Release him from custody
and put him
on the next plane out.
Sir, there's more going on here.
I know it.
Here's what I think is going on.
An ambitious lady cop
takes a position
in a shithole post
out in the middle of nowhere.
Hoping to make a name
for herself,
she seizes on the dumb actions
of an American tourist.
She'll arrest this missionary,
save the islanders
from this pernicious influence.
And then be rewarded
with a big promotion.
All the while neglecting
her husband
on the mainland.
Do I have that about right,
sub-inspector?
(SIGHS)
JOHN: Guys, guys, guys.
(CHEERING, LAUGHING)
Hey, next year, I plan our trip.
It's been five years in a row
of hostels and crappy food.
Hey, John.
You got our map, right?
Huh?
Hey.
You okay, bud?
This whole trip
you seem a little down.
Yeah, I'm just...
I'm just trying
to figure out some stuff.
Dude, you're the most
figured out person we know.
-(DYLAN CHUCKLES)
-I'm just trying to,
you know, find my path.
Dude, we know your path.
-You're gonna live out
our dreams.
-ZACH: Yeah!
Don't do that.
Don't put that on me.
When we first started
on these trips,
it was about helping people
see God.
Yeah, and it still is.
Are we doing enough?
Are we taking enough risks?
Is this as far
as we're willing to go?
John!
What the guys mean is, um...
Look, Katie and I
are trying to have kids.
And Zach is taking over
his dad's business.
And Dylan is moving to LA
to be the next Tom Cruise!
(LAUGHTER)
You're the Highlander,
my friend.
You're the one.
-I'm the one.
-(GROUP CHEERS)
(LAUGHTER)
Hey, hey, hey.
To John.
-To John.
DYLAN: Ah.
All right. Well, I guess that...
-Oh!
-(CHEERING)
-Yes!
-There it is.
(GENTLE WHOOPING)
There it goes. (CHUCKLES)
Your turn.
No more third-world countries...
-...please?
-He's right.
You know, aim for Sweden.
-No--
-I wanna meet my future wife.
Dude, it's so cold.
Guys!
Where do you wanna go, John?
WOMAN:
What is the Great Commission?
The Great Commission was given
to us by the Resurrected Christ,
who said, "Go and make disciples
of all nations."
This is a satellite video
of the highlands
of Papua New Guinea,
home to the Baruya Tribe.
These people
have never been told
about our Savior Jesus Christ,
but one day, one of you...
YOUNG WOMAN: Come on!
WOMAN:
...you're going to change that.
-YOUNG WOMAN: Wait!
-(GROUP CHATTERING)
WOMAN: We have God on our side.
But that doesn't mean things
won't go wrong,
because they will.
(GROUP CHATTERING)
WOMAN:
How will you share the gospel
if you get injured,
and there's no hospital?
-YOUNG MAN: Let's go!
-(SCATTERED CHATTER)
WOMAN: How will you persevere
if you're lost and need
to scavenge for food?
(PEOPLE CHEERING, SHOUTING)
WOMAN: What will you do
if you get stranded
in an active war zone
-miles from the border?
-(ENGINE STARTS)
GROUP: Yes!
-MAN 1: Let's go.
-MAN 2: Sweet!
-WOMAN: If you plan to travel...
-MAN 2: Bye, y'all!
...to the darkest corners
of the globe,
you must train to survive.
Because one day,
these skills
might just save your life.
Hey, guys, check it out.
We can camp here for the night.
Let's go.
YOUNG MAN:
Looks all right to me.
(GRUNTS, SHOUT, GASPS)
(MISSIONARIES SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
-(WOMAN SHOUTS)
-(JOHN GRUNTS)
-(WOMAN GROANS)
-(JOHN SIGHS)
-John?
-Yeah.
WOMAN: Let's stay by the water.
(JOHN CLEARS THROAT)
(CHANTING IN DISTANCE)
(CHANTING GROWS LOUDER)
(ALL CHANTING)
(SCREAMS)
-(SHOUTS)
-(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(CHANTING)
(SHOUTS)
(CHANTS)
Our Father, who art in heaven,
Hallowed be Thy name.
Thy--
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(IMITATES CHANTING)
(REPEATS CHANTING)
-(CROWD STOPS CHANTING)
-(JOHN REPEATS CHANT SLOWLY)
(REPEATS WORD, SIGHS)
-(SCOFFS)
-(MAN CHUCKLES)
-(JOHN REPEATS WORD)
-(GROUP CHUCKLES)
(GROUP CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
(VEHICLE APPROACHES)
(BRAKES SQUEAK)
JOHN: Everything okay?
Is Mom okay?
Yeah, your mother's fine.
What happened to your car?
(SCOFFS) I...
I sold it to pay for the lawyer.
Those prescriptions I wrote...
...I didn't know
they were federal agents.
I'm trained
to help those in need.
But they entrapped me.
They suspended my license.
Leave it to God, Dad.
He's got a plan for you.
I promise.
I came to this country
with nothing.
The Church, what we believe,
it was a way to belong,
meet nice people.
Try to live the right way.
Your mother and I
have always supported you
to find your passion.
But this, a-a missionary?
It's too extreme.
You-You don't have
to be a doctor.
(STAMMERING)
But I want you
to come home with me.
You're tired.
You've been driving all night.
Come on,
let me get you a coffee.
Why are you doing this?
You--
You've always been a dreamer,
John.
That's okay.
But... it is time to wake up.
You used to dream, too, Dad.
What?
(CHEERING)
JOHN: The State Fair...
(CHUCKLES)
Your painting won first place.
Remember?
(CHATTERING, INDISTINCT)
JOHN: It was that sunrise.
Coming up in the sky
past the ship.
Or was it a sunset?
I could never tell.
It-It's just a painting.
(LAUGHS)
No.
(CHATTERING)
JOHN: I wanted
to live inside it.
To reach out and touch it.
Like if I could get beyond
that frame, it would take me
to another world.
There-There's no other world.
You shouldn't have
stopped painting, Dad.
Have a safe trip back.
GANALI:
"Lord, please bless
and protect my dad.
He doesn't see
that everything I do..."
"...is in your service.
For the Kingdom of God. God..."
(MUTTERS)
"Life is in your hands, Father.
Oh, God, please keep my plans
hidden from the forces
of darkness."
"Forces of darkness"?
That would be me. (CHUCKLES)
Shit!
Sh-- Uh-- (SCOFFS)
Shit.
(THUNDER CRACKS)
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS IN DISTANCE)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ELECTRIC GUITAR STRUMS)
(SONG PLAYS ON ELECTRIC GUITAR)
Don't get many visitors
out here.
Are you Raz?
You're a tour guide, yeah?
Entrepreneur.
Restauranteur.
And, yes, I lead trips
on the side.
Diving and snorkeling.
Ever taken anyone
to North Sentinel Island?
You must be joking.
What do you know
about people who live there?
The Sentinelese?
Nothing. I'm part Onge.
Different island,
different language,
different everything.
So you can't communicate
with them?
No one can.
They don't want to talk to us.
-Cardamom are they?
-Mm-hmm.
Here.
Oh, no. My husband bakes them.
He cooks for you?
No, I do the cooking.
Of course.
How many mobile phones
do you own?
RAZ: How many do you own?
GANILA: I've seen at least three
since I walked in here.
So either I'm a good businessman
or a gangster.
Yes?
And what sort of business
did you have with John Chau?
RAZ: Who?
Your address was
in his notebook.
Stop wasting my time.
RAZ: We had no business.
He asked for my assistance,
and I refused.
Why not help him?
Do you know what they'd do,
the North Sentinelese,
if he was to set foot
on their island?
They wouldn't just kill him.
They'd crush his skull
to free the spirit.
Then mount his body on a stake,
right on the beach.
(METAL CLATTERING)
RAZ: Would you blame them?
Someone coming in, uninvited.
All alone, invading their home.
(EXHALES)
This guy's really gotten
under your skin, hasn't he?
I'm simply enforcing the law.
Since when
did the police do that?
The Swan.
Excuse me?
It's a bar.
Near the Aberdeen bus terminus.
It's there if you look for it.
You'll find what you need.
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(QUIET CHATTER)
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
(LIGHT CHATTER)
(MUFFLED DRUMMING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
(GIRL CHUCKLES)
(DOOR SLAMS, MUFFLED)
(EXHALES, PANTING)
(RAGGED BREATHING, SNIFFLES)
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
John?
(LAUGHS)
(ROOSTER CROWS)
(DOGS BARKING)
CHANDLER: It's nice, man.
You look good,
you been working out?
-JOHN: Yeah. Yeah. A little bit.
-CHANDLER: Yeah?
-Yeah, I see it.
-(JOHN CHUCKLES)
JOHN: How's it all been going?
CHANDLER:
Well, they're burning
the rainforest down.
You know, all this trash
is coming downstream
from the bigger towns.
(MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO)
Other than that,
everything's great.
JOHN: Where's Kayla?
-She moved to Baltimore.
-(ROOSTER CROWS)
Married a Presbyterian minister.
Drives a Tesla.
Kayla?
Missionary life is hard, man.
Most people give it up
sooner than later.
Tudo bem? (LAUGHS)
So, um, you remember that map
on the wall?
-(PEOPLE SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
-Uh-huh.
Yeah, I'm thinking about
going somewhere.
(EXHALES)
Are you sure I need to know?
It's not gonna work.
Why not?
North Sentinel
is the Mount Everest
of the missionary world.
Exactly.
Start with something smaller.
(LAUGHS) I'm not--
I'm not thinking small.
I'm going big.
You're not ready.
I came all the way out here
to talk to you.
Do you have any idea
how much I prepped for this?
Listen to me.
This isn't the old days.
This stuff,
it's harder than ever.
Indian government
has gotten really good
at spotting fanatics.
They'll see you coming.
How?
By spending 30 seconds
on your Instagram.
There's Christian messaging
all the way through it.
Not to mention they'll see
where you went to school.
You know, the places
you trained, the organizations
you worked for.
You're a Jesus freak, John.
They're not
gonna hand you a visa.
They're gonna put your ass
on the next plane home.
I've just finished
my EMT qualifications.
I'm going to go
get all the inoculations.
I found a contact in Jaipur
who knows a guy in Port Blair.
Everything is arranged.
Then you fucking un-arrange it.
(SIGHS) Look, you can start by
scrubbing Jesus
from your social media.
All right? You take six months,
nine months.
Go dark. Go secular.
Stop talking to people.
Stop bragging
about what you're going to do.
Show some restraint.
Look, I see you.
You wanna be that guy...
...who goes to Mordor.
But you gotta build him
the right way,
so the world believes it.
You know, you start over.
You build a hero.
All right, from today on,
this is the story
you're going to tell
about yourself.
And this will be the story
the world will know.
(MAN SINGING IN PORTUGUESE)
Hey, guys.
Another day in paradise.
Wish you were here.
Can't wait to show
you my adventures.
(MAN SINGING
IN PORTUGESE CONTINUES)
(REPEATING FOREIGN WORDS)
(SINGING CONTINUES)
It's another beautiful day.
We're just hiking along here.
Having a great time.
I couldn't ask
for anything more.
CHANDLER:
Man, I'm so proud of you.
Just remember, if it's not you,
then who?
If it's not now, then when?
You got this, man.
(MUSIC FADES)
(PHONE UNLOCKS)
(HUMMING)
(BIRD TITTERING)
(SNIFFS)
(PAN SIZZLING)
What's all this?
Jim and Denise are coming over.
But aren't they
bringing takeout?
John wanted my roast chicken.
He's home?
He's exhausted. He shaved
and went straight up
to his room.
JOHN:
So I look across the ridge,
I see black bear,
mama with cubs, 400 pounds.
I head the opposite direction.
I'm bushwhacking
along the trail,
and I just hear the...
(IMITATES RATTLE)
This diamondback
rears up its head and just...
(WHOOSH)
-...jabs me in the shin!
-I can't even imagine!
John,
you have to swing to church
and share your tales.
(DENISE LAUGHS)
They're starting to think
that I'm making it up
when I tell them.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
JIM: So how long you back for?
Uh, I'm headed off
again tomorrow.
DENISE:
Oh, that's not much time home.
Yeah, well, it's long enough
for Mom's cooking.
(SCOFFS)
And her washing machine.
-(BOTH CHUCKLE)
-Yeah.
-JIM: So, what else happened?
-JOHN: Mmm.
Well, I was hiking
along a different trail
this time...
JOHN:
Do you have any sunscreen
I can take?
LYNDA: Look in the closet.
Come here one minute.
Let me see.
Ah, no, I need more.
(CHUCKLES) Thank you.
I've had those on my wrist
since I was ten years old.
Just needed a new band.
And you weren't ten,
you were seven.
You know those
are Buddhist beads, right?
(LIGHT CHUCKLE)
I know. (CHUCKLES)
I just want you to be closer
to your heritage, you know?
To your dad.
(LYNDA SPEAKING, INDISTINCT)
(JOHN SPEAKING, INDISTINCT)
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
-LYNDA: That will do it.
-JOHN: Yeah.
JOHN: I'm still here.
LYNDA: The beads are still here.
(QUIET CONVERSATION CONTINUES)
-(TELEVISION CLICKS ON)
-(LIGHT MUSIC PLAYS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
ANNOUNCER:
You flip but they flop.
Now your pancakes are a mess.
And all that butter and fat
to cook 'em?
There's got to be a better way!
Introducing
the Perfect Pancake,
the world's first spatula-free
pancake maker.
The Perfect Pancake...
(CLICKS LIGHTSWITCH)
(CLICKS)
(GASPS)
(JET WHIRS)
OFFICER: Enjoy your stay.
Next.
Documents?
What is your purpose
to visit India?
Vacation.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
Flight 104 from Jaipur
to Mumbai...
Where do you intend to go?
Touring Jaipur.
Then south to Goa. Beaches.
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you.
(ANNOUNCERS CONTINUE,
INDISTINCT)
Next. Passport?
(INAUDIBLE)
(MOTOR WHIRS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(ENGINE STOPS)
Hi, sorry.
(CHATTER IN DISTANCE)
(HORNS HONKING)
MAN:
What the hell is wrong
with you people?
How long has this John...
whatever-his-name-is
been missing?
Ah. I give you a monkey's job.
Now the American Embassy
is calling about this kid.
The media is calling
about this kid.
The Lieutenant Governor in Delhi
knows about this kid!
I've been treating this
as a top priority, huh?
I need more resources.
You... lazy shit!
They're a UNESCO designated
indigenous tribe.
You've got warships,
attack helicopters, coast guard.
What the hell else do you need?
I've been studying
this boy's journal.
He may still be here
in Port Blair.
He may be waiting
to leave at night.
Go find him.
(SPEAKS HINDI)
Come on! (SPEAKS HINDI)
Let's go.
(SIRENS WAILING)
-(ENGINES REVVING)
-(SIRENS WAIL)
Madam, you again?
-(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
-(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
Sir, please.
Sir, what--
-Come, let's go.
-(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(CHATTERING)
Sir. Sir, I told you
he checked out.
There's nothing in here, sir.
Sir!
Then find out where he went,
who he talked to,
what he was last wearing.
I want everything
you have on this guy.
Yes, sir.
Don't just sit there
looking stupid!
Go and arrest those fishermen.
Fill up the jail.
Pretend like you actually
have a job to do!
FARID: Yes, sir.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER CONTINUES)
Maybe if you'd tried being nicer
to the witnesses,
they'd cooperate.
Never knew you had
a sense of humor.
I learned it from you.
That's new.
What?
The wedding ring.
I've always had it.
Just never worn it.
If I may, should we not
get back to solving the case?
(EXHALES)
Who says we're not?
What you're doing is theater.
And you know it.
-(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
-(CROWD CHATTERING)
There's a local fixer.
His name is Raz.
Do you know him?
If John Chau went
to anybody for help,
it's this fellow.
I know Raz.
RAZ: I want three thousand.
(LOUDLY) Three thou--?
(JOHN SCOFFS, CHUCKLES QUIETLY)
Three thousand dollars?
North Sentinel's barely
30 miles from here.
If it's so easy, get a kayak.
Good luck with the currents.
Good luck with the coast guards.
I can pay you 600.
(SCOFFS)
What is it with you guys?
Ah? You travel halfway
across the world
because you think
it's your job to save people.
What if we came to America
and did that to you?
I forgot, you're already saved.
You walk away,
you're sending
these people to hell.
Missionaries tried
to save my people.
Do I look saved?
It's never too late.
No. No, no, no.
You think this hardcore
Christian shit is going
to make people accept you?
No matter what you do,
you will always be
a Chink to them.
Six hundred's all I've got.
Let me see that.
(INHALES, EXHALES)
Hey.
Bring this to the wharf tonight.
There's a crew
who go out fishing at night.
They're Christian, too.
They'll get me all the way
over there for 300?
Not all the way.
Not to the beach. That's crazy.
But they'll get you close.
Quarter-mile off shore.
From there you go
the rest of the way alone.
Thank you.
-(THUNDER RUMBLES)
-Are you sure?
(DOGS BARKING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Ishaan, suspect's heading north
your way.
Farid, there is a river west
to Ishaan's road.
Start sweeping
for anything suspicious.
On my way.
Madam, we cleared both
the road and river
from suspect's house to here.
There's nothing.
The only other place
is the shrimping dock
on the other side.
Meet me there.
(SIREN WAILS)
(SIREN CONTINUES, STOPS)
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
-(ENGINE SPUTTERS, STARTS)
-Hey!
Hey!
Ishaan, cover the southeast side
of the shipping dock.
(SIREN WAILING)
Call coast guard.
It's a red speedboat.
It's heading out to sea.
Sir, it's him.
It's a red speedboat.
You saw him?
You saw it was John Chau?
The boat was hiding there, sir.
Then you did not
make a positive identification.
It's pitch dark out there.
Who else could it be?
Smugglers use these coves
dropping off refugees
from Bangladesh.
Don't you know that?
Sir, John Chau is getting away.
What has come over you?
Indian people, our people,
are routinely victimized
by crime here in Port Blair.
And you've become obsessed
with this one stupid
American boy?
I don't care about
the American boy.
It's the Sentinelese I care for.
All they want is to be
who they are.
Yet the world is determined
to go there and destroy them.
And someday they will.
So what? Do nothing?
You are a lazy shit.
Why are you even here?
Oh, I forgot.
You were given a monkey's job.
I wonder why.
This is my jurisdiction,
not yours.
You had no authorization
to deploy my officers out here.
Now go back to the station
and turn in your badge.
You're fired.
Y-You cannot be serious.
All this hot air from you,
and only one thing
you've said is true.
This is theater.
All of it.
John Chau is dead.
(INAUDIBLE)
(BUBBLING)
(GASPS)
(COUGHS)
(COUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(SNIFFLING)
(GRUNTING)
(QUIETLY PANTING)
-(LIGHT ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
-(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
YOUNG MAN: That's funny.
WOMAN 1: I can't believe it.
MAN: Hello. Thanks, mate.
(CONVERSATION CONTINUES,
INDISTINCT)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(WOMAN CHATTERING) Oh, shit!
Oh, my God!
Hey. Hey! Here. Take a seat.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, grab a seat.
Guys! Grab it. Grab my drink.
(GASPING, LAUGHING)
-You're getting soaked.
-WOMAN 1: Oh, my God!
(GROANING)
Oh, my God.
-Thanks, man.
-JOHN: All good.
Every day it rains at 2:00 p.m.,
like clockwork.
By 2:15, it'll be sunny again.
I love it. (LAUGHS)
MAN: It's pissing down.
We crashed your party now.
-You're all alone?
-Yeah.
MAN: I envy you.
It's been ten long days
with this lot.
WOMAN 2: Piss off.
Where to? It's piss-pouring.
I'm Melanie, by the way.
John.
Looks like you've had yourself
quite the morning.
MAN: Shit.
What's up?
It's the rental car.
Don't tell me
it's fallen through.
No, it's reserved...
but it's a manual shift.
-Caleb!
-MAN: I couldn't tell.
It didn't say anything about
whether it was a manual
or an auto.
-Oh, my--
-Well, does anybody drive stick?
No!
-MELANIE: What do you reckon?
-None of us.
MELANIE: Caleb.
-You drive a manual?
-Yeah.
-You-- Would you?
-Yes! We're on.
Yeah. Come on.
You are a legend.
(LAUGHS)
Thanks for doing this, mate.
You're a real godsend.
You sure
we're not taking you away
from anything?
No.
Positive?
It's all good.
Hold on!
-Whoa! Shit!
-(WOMEN SCREAMING, LAUGHING)
WOMAN 1: Whoa!
Oh! (LAUGHS)
Nice spot.
Who's up for a swim?
We can do better.
Why not?
JOHN: All right.
Just a little bit further.
Come on.
CALEB: Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
(WOMAN 1: INHALES)
-Oh, my God!
-You're a legend.
What?
WOMAN 1: Wow.
See? Better.
Yeah.
But how do we get down there?
Like this.
-No!
-(JOHN HOOTS)
Well, it was nice knowing him.
(GRUNTS)
-Holy shit.
-Oh, my God.
-He's insane.
-(LAUGHS)
He's insane.
Well. Shit. (SCREAMS)
-Melanie!
Oh!
(LAUGHS)
(SQUEALS)
-Oh, my God!
-Whoo!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(SHRIEKS)
Hey!
Wait for me.
Oh, you cowards! (LAUGHS)
All right, then. Their loss.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on!
Oh, my God! (SHRIEKS)
(CHATTERING)
MELANIE: Beer?
No. Thanks.
(SIGHS)
Look at 'em.
No idea where they are.
And tomorrow, it's just...
on to the next amusement.
So, I have a game.
(CHUCKLES)
Actually, no, it's stupid.
No!
What is it?
Right, well...
I ask you a question,
then you ask me one.
Nothing ever gets answered.
-Okay.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mmm.
-(EXHALES)
-What's your favorite... color?
-Oh.
What's your greatest fear?
Why do you ask?
Who taught you to stick shift?
What do you wanna
do with your life?
How come you've got epinephrine
in your backpack?
Why did you follow me off
the waterfall?
(CHUCKLES)
MELANIE:
Have you got a favorite scar?
JOHN: Is one of those guys
your boyfriend?
Have you seen the ice machine
in my hotel?
I don't mean to rush, but
they could be back
any minute now.
You got a condom?
It's okay. Caleb has some.
Two secs.
Yep. Bingo.
You're shivering.
It's like a hundred degrees
in here. Are you...
You okay?
Do you...
do you not want to do this?
-(WHISPERS) No... I do.
-Okay.
Hey.
Is this your first time?
What?
It's okay.
It's everyone's first time
at some point, right?
No. Uh...
It's not that.
Uh... (SCOFFS)
It's just...
A kid shot me this morning.
What?
I don't understand.
(SCOFFS)
He shot me with an arrow.
It was right when I thought
I was getting through to them.
To who?
The North Sentinelese.
I was there. This morning.
No sense in lying.
It feels so good to tell you.
(CALEB, DRUNKEN SINGING)
Can I please have
some privacy for once?
(BOTH GIGGLING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
John,
what are you talking about?
Why were you on that island?
To share the Lord's word.
You're a missionary?
These people don't know
about Jesus Christ.
And you came here
to convert them.
To save them.
(SNIFFLES) I sensed there was
something different about you.
But never would have
guessed this one.
-I'm trying to help them.
-Help them?
Have you ever heard the term
"human safari"?
Yes, yes, of course I have.
I love the North Sentinelese.
I wouldn't hurt them.
Do you know what
Western imperialism has done
to this part of the world?
Almost every tribe
has gone extinct
after contact with the West.
I've taken the precautions.
I'm inoculated.
They were stolen.
Experimented on.
And whoever did survive,
whoever wasn't wiped out
by disease--
Look at me! Am I some scary guy?
What you're doing is disgusting.
You're partying on their beach.
Fair enough. Yeah. Yes.
But how can you
not see the problem
with what you're doing?
I mean, you say you love
the North Sentinelese.
You don't know
the first thing about them.
Hey, I've done the research.
I know the history.
They're living in darkness.
They are lost.
You need to go.
(GASPING)
What are you trying to prove?
(INAUDIBLE)
Just another day
in paradise here.
(QUIETLY)
What you are doing
is disgusting.
What you're doing is disgusting.
(SHOUTS)
What you're doing is disgusting!
(PANTING, STOPS)
(PHONE RINGS)
-(SIGHS)
-(RINGS)
What is it?
Inspector Ganali,
this is Steve Simon,
US Consulate.
Who?
Oh... you.
SIMON: Anything on John Chau?
What do you think
I've been doing all this time?
SIMON: Let's play a game here.
Let's say he's dead.
Yeah, that's
what people seem to think.
SIMON:
Any chance you guys
can get his body back?
Or... is that a whole thing?
Do you know what is
even better than his body?
His journal.
Let me try
and read it out to you.
"God,
I thank you for choosing me
even before I was even formed
in my mother's womb
as your messenger
of the Good News to the people
of North Sentinel Island."
How noble of him.
Or this...
"God, I do not wish to die.
Who will take my place if I do?"
This is not about God!
He does not know the tribe!
He doesn't know anything!
(SIGHS)
He's just lost.
SIMON: Still there?
Yeah.
I'm still here. (SIGHS)
Thank you, Steve Simon.
(BEEPS)
Come in, Coast Guard Center.
Andaman Coast Guard, go ahead.
This is Inspector Ganali,
Port Blair Police.
I'm requesting for
a search and rescue helicopter
to take me to
North Sentinel at first light.
Mel? Mel!
Melanie! Hey.
I'm sorry. Um...
(GASPS) Be right back.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-(HORN HONKS)
-Headed out?
Uh, Thailand, yeah.
-About last night, I'm sorry.
-It's fine.
It's okay.
I've never met anybody
like you before.
Okay.
So yesterday, when I got shot...
...the Bible was in my vest.
It saved my life.
That's good. That's good.
So, like,
it literally stopped the arrow.
So, last night I opened it up.
You know, I wanted
to see where the arrow stopped.
Which verse.
It was Isaiah 65.
"I revealed myself to those
who did not ask for me.
I was found by those
who did not seek me."
Okay.
I was thinking, like,
how incredible is that?
The arrow would stop
the missionary's creed.
It's gotta be a sign, right?
And then I realized something,
okay?
I realized
it wasn't the North Sentinelese
I revealed myself to.
That was a total fail.
It was you.
I revealed myself to you.
You were right.
I don't need to go back
to that island.
Someone else can try.
I wanna come with you.
John, I told the police.
What?
After you left, I was worried.
Uh, what did you say to them?
Oi, Mel. We're leaving.
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
You're gonna get me arrested.
I didn't know
what else to do, John.
I'm-I'm totally screwed.
I have to go.
Wait. W-When's your flight?
Now. Soon.
We're headed to the airport.
I'll meet you there.
(ANNOUNCER, INDISTINCT)
JOHN: Melanie!
CHANDLER: Yo, John!
Chandler?
You all right?
W-What are you doing here?
I came to see you. Remember?
Hey, don't tell me
you're leaving already.
(SCOFFS)
Dude, I need
to hear about everything.
Forget about her. There's plenty
of chicks out there
who dig Christian guys.
-Yep.
-Look how far you got.
You actually made it
to the island.
You preached in the waves, man.
You can go home without shame.
Home to what?
What am I supposed to do now?
Anything you want.
Like I said, this kind of thing
isn't for most people, okay?
When Jesus asked those fishermen
in the Sea of Galilee
to follow him,
how many guys do you think
he had to go to before
he found 12 that said yes?
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
Yes! Yes, of course
it's supposed
to make you feel better.
You're a human being.
And the demands that Christ
makes on us,
they're unreasonable.
At least you tried.
You know?
Take it.
-Your backpack?
-I don't need it anymore.
There's a plane
leaving for Bangkok
in 45 minutes. Get on it.
What do you mean?
I just got here.
The police know about me.
Soon they'll know about you.
But I need some money.
Three hundred should be enough
to find a boat.
Dude, you're--
Are you for real?
You seriously thinking
of going back?
TICKET AGENT:
There's a flight just right now.
Here, you better hurry.
Thank you.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT)
(HORNS HONKING)
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(ANNOUNCEMENTS IN HINDI)
("RHYMES OF AN HOUR"
BY MAZZY STAR PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SONG CONTINUES)
(INDISTINCT)
...as I have everybody's
undivided attention,
-once a week.
-(CHUCKLING)
Where's our son, Lynda?
...everything I say.
Where's our son?
Where's John?
PASTOR:
...it's coming out
of her mouth and mine.
-(LAUGHTER)
-(PASTOR CONTINUES, INIDISTINCT)
(LAUGHTER)
(BEEPS)
(SONG CONTINUES)
Hey, guys.
This is it.
About to be dropped off for good
on North Sentinel.
(INHALES)
I hope this isn't the last
you hear from me.
But if it is...
just remember...
...first one to heaven wins.
(ENGINE REVS, BRAKES SQUEAL)
(SONG CONTINUES)
Patrick.
Are you all right?
(RAGGED BREATHING)
What did we do wrong?
What do you mean?
(RAGGED BREATH)
We should have stopped him.
We let him get farther
and farther away.
God only knows where he is now.
Patrick.
You know where he is.
We've known for years
what John was going to do.
And now that he's there,
he needs our prayers.
Because if anyone
can pull this off,
it's our son.
-What?
-Some people are coming over.
We're holding
a prayer group for John.
(GASPS)
Okay?
(WAVES WHOOSHING)
(BOAT ENGINE HUMMING)
(VEHICLE ENGINE HUMS)
(ENGINE REVS)
SONNY:
You're not a police officer
anymore.
I could have you jailed
for this.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Are you going to ignore me
like you ignore your husband?
I don't have a husband.
I'm not married.
It was a stupid story
I made up for you people!
The one I love
refuses to marry me
because her religion,
our religion, won't permit her
to become my wife.
Now do you understand
you stupid son of a bitch?
There's no word in Hindi
for who I am.
John Chau had no place
in this world either.
So he came here.
That's what people do
when they're lost.
They end up here.
If the police say a man is dead,
that man will be dead.
If the poilce say
a man is merely missing,
his relatives and friends
may live in hope.
It's up to you.
(BIRDS TWEETING)
(BIRDS, PARROTS SQUAWKING)
(SOUND FADES)
(BIRDS SINGING)
(SIGHS)
(BIRD CAWS)
-(RUSTLING)
-(BIRD CAWING)
-(BIRDS CAWING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
Hello. (SIGHS)
I'm John.
-(ARROWS SCRAPE)
-(BOWS STRETCH)
(BREATH CATCHES)
-Um... S--
-(FLIPS PAGES)
(INAUDIBLE)
Oh, Dad.
John.
(HELICOPTER BLADES BEAT)
(HELICOPTER WHIRS)
MAN: One, two, three.
("LIVE FOREVER"
BY BILLY JOE SHAVER PLAYING)
(SONG STOPS)